<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>NameQuick Updates</title>
        <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>Version 1.9.28</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <h1 id="namequick-v1.9.28">NameQuick v1.9.28</h1>
<h2 id="pro-tip">Pro Tip</h2>
<p>💡 <strong>Speed up file processing</strong>: Deactivate meta
description generation in settings when not needed. This can
significantly reduce processing time and token usage, especially for
large batches of files. Only enable it when you specifically need
detailed metadata extraction.</p>
<h2 id="whats-fixed">What’s Fixed</h2>
<h3 id="no-more-infinite-loading-spinners">No More Infinite Loading
Spinners</h3>
<p>Fixed a frustrating issue where image previews would occasionally get
stuck with spinning loading indicators that never completed. NameQuick
now has bulletproof timeout handling that ensures all images load
properly or gracefully show an error message.</p>
<h3 id="better-memory-management">Better Memory Management</h3>
<p>• Significantly improved memory usage when processing large batches
of images • Smarter cache management prevents memory pressure on older
Macs • More efficient image loading reduces CPU usage during preview
generation</p>
<h2 id="whats-improved">What’s Improved</h2>
<h3 id="faster-image-loading">Faster Image Loading</h3>
<p>• <strong>3x faster</strong> thumbnail generation with new
progressive loading system • Images now appear instantly in low quality,
then sharpen automatically • Better caching means images you’ve seen
before load instantly • Reduced memory footprint when working with
high-resolution screenshots</p>
<h3 id="more-reliable-performance">More Reliable Performance</h3>
<p>• Eliminated rare crashes during heavy image processing workloads •
Better error recovery when images fail to load or are corrupted •
Streamlined background processing reduces interference with other apps •
Improved stability when switching between different file types</p>
<h3 id="cleaner-user-interface">Cleaner User Interface</h3>
<p>• Removed unnecessary debug information from production builds •
Faster app startup with optimized initialization process • More
responsive image previews that adapt to available system resources •
Better handling of very large images without UI freezing</p>
<h3 id="enhanced-debugging-tools">Enhanced Debugging Tools</h3>
<p>• New cache statistics overlay for troubleshooting (available in
debug builds) • Better logging helps identify performance bottlenecks •
Simplified timeout configuration for advanced users • Improved error
messages with clearer descriptions</p>
<h3 id="smarter-image-compression">Smarter Image Compression</h3>
<p>• <strong>New intelligent compression system</strong> that preserves
image quality • Automatically detects already-compressed images to avoid
quality loss • Better support for modern image formats including HEIC
from iPhone photos • Reduced API request sizes for faster AI processing
• Fixed rare compression failures with very large images</p>
<h2 id="behind-the-scenes">Behind the Scenes</h2>
<p>This release includes a comprehensive refactoring of NameQuick’s
image handling system. While invisible to most users, these improvements
create a more stable foundation for future features and ensure NameQuick
performs consistently across all Mac configurations.</p>
<p>The new unified file encoding system ensures all AI services (OpenAI,
Gemini, Ollama) handle images consistently, reducing bugs and improving
reliability across the board.</p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 07:47:17 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure
                url="https://josimou.github.io/NameQuick-Releases/updates/NameQuick-1.9.28.dmg"
                sparkle:version="102"
                sparkle:shortVersionString="1.9.28"
                length="9346941"
                type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="iikm4jY1igIkU8SGFTcQVBv4B2yr2c8waylovvySEe9Wq/+2euschq9snyT+RGYXoEnrgD/RqPkZHsbG1BxiAA=="
            />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
