<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>NameQuick Updates</title>
        <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>Version 2.0.14</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <h1 id="namequick-v2.0.14">NameQuick v2.0.14</h1>
<p>This release adds a redesigned templates grid with quick create and
inline edits, plus layout polish and stability fixes.</p>
<h2 id="highlights">Highlights</h2>
<ul>
<li>Watch folders: Instant delete sync from Finder with immediate list
update.</li>
<li>Adds a redesigned templates grid with a dedicated “New Template”
card.</li>
<li>Enables inline renaming directly on template cards.</li>
<li>Shows key fields at a glance; extra fields open in a popover.</li>
<li>Improves grid stability for consistent card sizes.</li>
<li>Extraction and post-processing fields: Uninterrupted typing — no
more focus loss after the first character.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="new">New</h2>
<ul>
<li>Templates grid: Browse templates in a clean, responsive grid
(Templates tab).</li>
<li>“New Template” card: Create a template from the first slot.</li>
<li>Inline renaming: Double‑click a card title to rename.</li>
<li>Field chips: View key fields; open a popover for the full list.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="improvements">Improvements</h2>
<ul>
<li>Template cards
<ul>
<li>Standardizes sizing for consistent rows.</li>
<li>Refines hover states and centers “New Template” content.</li>
<li>Moves actions to an overflow menu while keeping right‑click.</li>
</ul></li>
<li>Template editor
<ul>
<li>Clarifies sections for extraction, formatting, and transforms.</li>
<li>Adds contextual help popovers for quick guidance.</li>
</ul></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="fixes">Fixes</h2>
<ul>
<li>Prevents grid reflow caused by varying description or field
lengths.</li>
<li>Keeps chip row height consistent for better alignment.</li>
<li>Maintains centered layout on the “New Template” card.</li>
</ul>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:06:30 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure
                url="https://josimou.github.io/NameQuick-Releases/updates/NameQuick-2.0.14.dmg"
                sparkle:version="137"
                sparkle:shortVersionString="2.0.14"
                length="13850518"
                type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="WnMeYEORRS5hw9DrC7JS8TxJjDl9nH+5BcIjOCtwhy4bU6SMnWFQsN1INH0vFxbB5xuj97hmGfiDSNa2ATVnDA=="
            />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
