<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>NameQuick Updates</title>
        <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>Version 1.9.20</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <h1 id="namequick-v1.9.20-release-notes">NameQuick v1.9.20 Release
Notes</h1>
<h2 id="uiux-improvements">🎨 UI/UX Improvements</h2>
<p><strong>Streamlined Settings</strong> - Reduced from 9+ tabs to just
5 focused sections. Everything is now exactly where you’d expect it to
be, making configuration faster and more intuitive.</p>
<p><strong>Visual Processing Indicators</strong> - New animated badges
and status chips show exactly what’s happening with your files.
Color-coded mode indicators make it clear whether you’re using Smart
Rename or Template processing.</p>
<p><strong>Cleaner, More Professional Look</strong> - Every element has
been refined with a modern design system. The interface feels more
polished and consistent throughout.</p>
<p><strong>Better Information Architecture</strong> - Completely
reorganized how features are presented. The app now guides you naturally
from selecting files to choosing processing methods to seeing
results.</p>
<h2 id="performance-reliability">⚡ Performance &amp; Reliability</h2>
<p><strong>More Reliable AI Processing</strong> - If one AI service is
down, NameQuick automatically switches to another. Temporary glitches
are handled gracefully with smart retries.</p>
<p><strong>Improved Large File Handling</strong> - Smart sampling
technology processes large documents more efficiently while maintaining
accuracy.</p>
<h2 id="under-the-hood">🔧 Under the Hood</h2>
<p><strong>Faster and More Responsive</strong> - Rebuilt with modern
Swift concurrency for better performance. File processing is noticeably
snappier.</p>
<p><strong>Rock-Solid Stability</strong> - Extensive testing ensures
this release is our most reliable yet. We’ve squashed numerous edge-case
bugs.</p>
<h2 id="bug-fixes">🐛 Bug Fixes</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fixed missing processing indicators on file thumbnails</li>
<li>Resolved settings navigation issues that made some options hard to
find</li>
<li>Fixed license unlinking functionality now accessible from Settings
&gt; About</li>
<li>Corrected API integration issues causing authentication
failures</li>
<li>Fixed file permissions not being properly respected during
processing</li>
<li>Resolved memory leaks during batch processing operations</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="notes">📝 Notes</h2>
<p>This is a major architectural update that sets the foundation for
exciting features coming in 2025. While maintaining full compatibility
with existing workflows, we’ve made NameQuick more reliable, more
intuitive, and ready for the future.</p>
<p><strong>Important for existing users</strong>: Your settings and
templates are preserved, though you may notice they’ve been reorganized
for better clarity. All your existing licenses and API keys continue to
work exactly as before.</p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:09:52 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure
                url="https://josimou.github.io/NameQuick-Releases/updates/NameQuick-1.9.20.dmg"
                sparkle:version="74"
                sparkle:shortVersionString="1.9.20"
                length="7564752"
                type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="3rFnV7jUFLJN5rMF3L7nVbhS6wmVp3XXiXysADv/4P0+zLHpko7CFpeTQLPpjBdwVJVnrd6dkHbQAfFED/2mAQ=="
            />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
