<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>NameQuick Updates</title>
        <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>Version 2.0.11</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <h1 id="namequick-v2.0.11">NameQuick v2.0.11</h1>
<p>This update focuses on making file processing more reliable,
especially for downloaded files and larger batches.</p>
<h2 id="new">New</h2>
<ul>
<li>Cancel Processing (new): stop the current run instantly without
creating errors.
<ul>
<li>What happens: the active file stops; all queued files clear; no
error pop‑ups.</li>
<li>Safe to retry: cancelled files aren’t marked failed — just run again
when ready.</li>
<li>Where to find it: toolbar (X), menu bar (Cancel All), batch window
(Cancel All).</li>
</ul></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="whats-fixed">What’s Fixed</h2>
<ul>
<li>Files you download now get processed more consistently. No more
wondering if that screenshot or document will show up.</li>
<li>Better handling when you drag &amp; drop files that are already in
your library. They get reprocessed without confusion.</li>
<li>Improved stability during busy periods when lots of files are being
discovered at once.</li>
<li>File monitoring is more precise, catching changes that were
sometimes missed before.</li>
<li>Issues button now reliably opens the Issues HUD again, so you can
review and clear errors directly.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="under-the-hood">Under the Hood</h2>
<ul>
<li>Enhanced the way NameQuick tracks files through the processing
pipeline.</li>
<li>Better coordination between different parts of the app when handling
file batches.</li>
<li>More reliable database operations, especially during high-volume
imports.</li>
<li>Smarter duplicate detection to avoid unnecessary work.</li>
</ul>
<p>This should make NameQuick feel more predictable, especially if you
work with lots of files or frequently download content that needs
processing.</p>
<p>— Josef</p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 23:35:06 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure
                url="https://josimou.github.io/NameQuick-Releases/updates/NameQuick-2.0.11.dmg"
                sparkle:version="135"
                sparkle:shortVersionString="2.0.11"
                length="13597072"
                type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="03Mf+Fdz5vaMzVPYSwosXL8VStr0OAa9C42r0fI19AA5gGnX7A5wH5YCAyeEBRe0Shih4pfJZ1c13zPOFTtMBQ=="
            />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
