<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>NameQuick Updates</title>
        <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>Version 1.9.21</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <h1 id="namequick-v1.9.21-release-notes">NameQuick v1.9.21 Release
Notes</h1>
<h2 id="bug-fixes">Bug Fixes</h2>
<h3 id="template-transformation-rules">Template Transformation
Rules</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Fixed: Only first transformation rule was being
applied</strong> - When you added multiple transformation rules to a
template (like “Convert to lowercase” and “Replace spaces with dashes”),
only the first rule would work. Now all rules are applied in the order
you specified.</li>
<li><strong>Fixed: Template save button not responding</strong> - The
save button would sometimes become unresponsive when editing templates
with transformation rules. This has been resolved with improved state
management.</li>
<li><strong>Fixed: UI refresh issues when editing transformation
rules</strong> - The template editor now properly updates when adding or
modifying post-processing rules, ensuring a smooth editing
experience.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="file-renaming-issues">File Renaming Issues</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Fixed: Files wouldn’t rename when only changing letter
case</strong> - Previously, renaming “Invoice.PDF” to “invoice.pdf”
would fail silently. This has been fixed - case-only renames now work
properly.</li>
<li><strong>Fixed: Some renamed files weren’t actually changing on
disk</strong> - In certain situations, NameQuick would show a file as
renamed but the actual file wouldn’t change. This has been
resolved.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="ai-provider-improvements">AI Provider Improvements</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Fixed: Template processing reliability</strong> - Resolved
issues where templates would sometimes fail to generate the expected
filename format, particularly with Gemini and OpenAI providers.</li>
<li><strong>Improved: Gemini error messages</strong> - HTTP 400 errors
from Gemini now provide specific, actionable guidance:
<ul>
<li>Schema validation errors suggest simplifying template fields</li>
<li>API key errors direct users to verify their credentials</li>
<li>Quota errors point to Google Cloud Console for usage details</li>
<li>File format errors suggest trying different files</li>
</ul></li>
</ul>
<h3 id="ollama-integration">Ollama Integration</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>New: Structured outputs support</strong> - Implemented
Ollama’s structured outputs feature for improved reliability:
<ul>
<li>All models running Ollama v0.5+ now support JSON schema-based
outputs</li>
<li>LLaVA models (including llava:7b) and moondream use structured
outputs by default</li>
<li>Automatic fallback to enhanced JSON prompts for older models</li>
</ul></li>
<li><strong>Enhanced: Date extraction reliability</strong> - Improved
date detection with comprehensive format examples:
<ul>
<li>Now recognizes ISO dates (2025-06-19), US/EU formats (06/19/2025,
19/06/2025)</li>
<li>Handles written dates (June 19, 2025), partial dates (June
2025)</li>
<li>Better detection of date indicators like “Invoice Date:”, “Due
Date:”, etc.</li>
<li>Clear instructions to return empty strings instead of “null” or
“N/A” when dates aren’t found</li>
</ul></li>
<li><strong>New: Model quality indicators</strong> - Added visual
guidance for model selection:
<ul>
<li>Star icon (green) for recommended models with high extraction
accuracy</li>
<li>Checkmark (blue) for models with good performance</li>
<li>Warning triangle (orange) for models that may have accuracy
issues</li>
<li>Helps users choose appropriate models for their extraction
needs</li>
</ul></li>
<li><strong>Fixed: Ollama timeout issues</strong> - Increased timeouts
to prevent failures with slower models:
<ul>
<li>Request timeout increased from 60 seconds to 5 minutes</li>
<li>Processing timeout for Ollama increased to match</li>
<li>Prevents “The request timed out” errors when using models like
moonshot</li>
</ul></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="technical-improvements">Technical Improvements</h2>
<ul>
<li>Refined animation handling in transformation editor for better
performance</li>
<li>Enhanced state synchronization between view models and UI
components</li>
<li>More robust error parsing and user-friendly error messages</li>
<li>Implemented Ollama’s GBNF grammar-based structured outputs for all
compatible models</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p><em>Thank you for your patience as we improve NameQuick! If you
encounter any issues, please report them at
support@namequick.cc</em></p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:13:26 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure
                url="https://josimou.github.io/NameQuick-Releases/updates/NameQuick-1.9.21.dmg"
                sparkle:version="76"
                sparkle:shortVersionString="1.9.21"
                length="7616443"
                type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="859AmuJS5++Fg0RmHoubLLCws5TLqUCFffAoxT13NMk3xRRKkrtOly1ayyorHC5rEol3E4+0/y0RlzEYge0FAg=="
            />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
