<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>NameQuick Updates</title>
        <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>Version 1.9.30</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <h1 id="namequick-v1.9.30-release-notes">NameQuick v1.9.30 Release
Notes</h1>
<h2 id="performance-update">Performance Update</h2>
<p>This update focuses on making NameQuick faster and more efficient.
The app can now handle large number of files easily.</p>
<h3 id="whats-changed">What’s Changed</h3>
<p><strong>Files Loading</strong> - Files load faster when you open the
app - Scrolling is smoother, especially with lots of files - The app
remembers which folders you use most and loads those first</p>
<p><strong>Search</strong> - Search is noticeably faster - Results show
up without delay - Works better with partial matches and typos</p>
<p><strong>Memory Usage</strong> - Uses less RAM - Doesn’t slow down
other apps as much - Handles large files collections better</p>
<p><strong>General Speed</strong> - App starts up faster - Everything
responds quicker when you click - Less waiting around for things to
happen</p>
<h3 id="bug-fixes">Bug Fixes</h3>
<ul>
<li>Fixed slowdowns that happened after using the app for a while</li>
<li>Fixed crashes with very large file collections</li>
<li>Better recovery when something goes wrong</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="whats-next">What’s Next</h3>
<p>This is the first step in the performance improvement journey. The
next update will include: - More performance enhancements - UI
improvements to make the app more intuitive and easier to use - Better
visual feedback for all operations</p>
<p>If you notice any issues with this update, please let me know.</p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:51:21 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure
                url="https://josimou.github.io/NameQuick-Releases/updates/NameQuick-1.9.30.dmg"
                sparkle:version="127"
                sparkle:shortVersionString="1.9.30"
                length="10618333"
                type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="jxuHGbf94u23uT9if2hR7XjI1DpEgkwHv9Of3Rg4kx1W+PR23XfwXtdrSkcBZ/CS4HZYmfyskZet1K/dlszBBw=="
            />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
