<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>NameQuick Updates</title>
        <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>Version 2.0.0</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <h1 id="namequick-v2.0.0">NameQuick v2.0.0</h1>
<p>This one’s big. I rebuilt a lot of NameQuick so it feels simpler,
steadier, and more predictable. You should notice it right away.</p>
<h2 id="whats-new">What’s New</h2>
<ul>
<li>UI that gets out of your way: clearer navigation, fewer clicks,
smarter defaults.</li>
<li>Results you can trust: better validation and error handling means
fewer hiccups and do‑overs.</li>
<li>Stays smooth under load: long sessions are calmer with fewer
surprises.</li>
<li>Subscription customers should see a significant boost in reliability
and consistency in the template feature.</li>
<li>BYOK + GPT‑5: if you bring your own key, the model picker now
includes GPT‑5 and a new “Reasoning Effort” dropdown. Start low, then
bump it up to balance speed, cost, and quality.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="templates">Templates</h2>
<ul>
<li>More breathing room and an editor that’s easier to set up.</li>
<li>Iterating is faster, and outputs are more consistent.</li>
<li>I’ll keep polishing this area - expect steady improvements.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="looking-ahead">Looking Ahead</h2>
<ul>
<li>With the heavy lift done, I can ship faster, smaller updates.</li>
<li>Public roadmap is back: vote or suggest ideas at
https://namequick.featurebase.app/roadmap</li>
<li>I’m also investing in better reliability for local models (they’re
tight on typical hardware, so this will land in steps).</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="feedback">Feedback</h2>
<ul>
<li>Easiest path: email support from Settings → About (add “Feedback” to
the subject).</li>
<li>Helpful details: your NameQuick version, macOS version, what you
expected vs. what happened, and a small sample template/output if you
can.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="thank-you">Thank You</h2>
<p>Thanks for sticking with me through this one. Your patience and
feedback made 2.0 possible.</p>
<p>— Josef</p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:09:14 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure
                url="https://josimou.github.io/NameQuick-Releases/updates/NameQuick-2.0.0.dmg"
                sparkle:version="132"
                sparkle:shortVersionString="2.0.0"
                length="13738677"
                type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="LGMYxrh656/Rll1N67TrLyKakqsRuhddVZMb/2mhcok0OmzM+YB1ikuiUSDnSDOh9mz5rwJECZsLBHJTAFB2Ag=="
            />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
